ballball.com 2013-10-14

# Privacy Policy - BallBall - Exclusive Football European Video Content App

Table of Contents:

  1. **INTRODUCTION**
  2. **COLLECTION OF INFORMATION**
  3. **USE AND DISCLOSURE**
  4. **SECURITY**
  5. **USER ACCESS AND CONTROL**
  6. **OTHER IMPORTANT INFORMATION**
  7. **CONTACT US**

**1\. INTRODUCTION**

_Ball Ball_ , owned and operated by NWS Digital Asia Pte. Limited (collectively, “ _Ball Ball_ ,” “our” or “we”) wants you to be familiar with how we collect, use and disclose information from and about you. This Privacy Policy describes our practices in connection with information collected through services such as websites, mobile sites, applications (“apps”), and widgets (collectively, the “Services”).

A list of our affiliated companies (“Company Affiliates”) is available at [News Corp](http://newscorp.com/about/).

As set forth in our [Terms of Use](http://www.ballball.com/terms-of-use), the Company Services are for a general audience, are not targeted to children, and do not knowingly collect personal information from individuals under 18 years of age.

This Privacy Policy applies to all users, including both those who use the Services without being registered with or subscribing to a Service and those who have registered with or subscribe to a Service. This Privacy Policy applies to our collection and use of your personal information (i.e., information that identifies a specific person, such as full name or email address). It also describes generally our practices for handling non-personal information (for example, interests, demographics and services usage).

By using the Services, you expressly consent to the collection, use and/or disclosure of your personal information by _Ball Ball_ in accordance with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, and your continued use of the Services will be deemed to be consent by you to the same.

**2\. COLLECTION OF INFORMATION**

We and our service providers collect the following information from and about you:

**Registration Information** is the information you submit to register for a Service, for example, to create an account or receive alerts. Registration Information may include, for example, name and email address.

**Public Information and Posts** consist of comments or content that you post to the Services and the information about you that accompanies those posts or content, which may include a name, user name, comments, likes, status, profile information and picture. Public Information and Posts are always public, which means they are available to everyone and may be displayed in search results on external search engines.

**Information from Social Media.** If you access or log-in to a Service through a social media service or connect a Service to a social media service, the information we collect may also include your user ID and/or user name associated with that social media service, any information or content you have permitted the social media service to share with us, such as your profile picture, email address or friends lists, and any information you have made public in connection with that social media service. When you access the _Ball Ball_ Services through social media services or when you connect a Service to social media services, you consent to the collection, storage, use and/or disclosure of such information and content by _Ball Ball_ in accordance with this Privacy Policy. __

**Activity Information.** When you access and interact with the _Ball Ball_ Services, we may collect certain information about those visits. For example, in order to permit your connection to the Services, our servers receive and record information about your computer, device, and browser, including potentially your IP address, browser type, and other software or hardware information. If you access the Services from a mobile or other device, we may collect a unique device identifier assigned to that device, geolocation data, or other transactional information for that device.

Cookies and other tracking technologies (such as browser cookies, pixels, beacons, and Adobe Flash technology including cookies) are comprised of small bits of data that often include a de-identified or anonymous unique identifier. Websites, apps and other services send this data to your browser when you first request a web page and then store the data on your computer so the website can access information when you make subsequent requests for pages from that service. These technologies may also be used to collect and store information about your usage of the Services, such as pages you have visited, content you have viewed, search queries you have run and advertisements you have seen.

Third parties that support the Services by serving advertisements or providing services, such as allowing you to share content or tracking aggregate Services usage statistics, may also use these technologies to collect similar information. _Ball Ball_ does not control these third-party technologies and their use is governed by the privacy policies of third parties using such technologies. For more information about third-party advertising networks and similar entities that use these technologies, see [www.aboutads.info/consumers](http://www.aboutads.info/consumers), and to opt-out of such ad networks’ and services’ advertising practices, go to [www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices).

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies, but you can change your settings to notify you when a cookie is being set or updated, or to block cookies altogether. Please consult the “Help” section of your browser for more information. Users can manage the use of Flash technologies, with the Flash management tools available at Adobe’s website, see <http://www.adobe.com/devnet/security.html> Please note that by blocking any or all cookies you may not have access to certain features, content or personalization available through the _Ball Ball_ Services.

**Information from Other Sources.** We may supplement the information we collect with information from other sources, such as publicly available information from social media services, commercially available sources and information from our Company Affiliates or business partners.

**3\. USE AND DISCLOSURE**

We use the information we collect from and about you to provide the _Ball Ball_ Services and features to you, including: to measure and improve those Services and features; to improve your experience with both online and off-line Services by delivering content you will find relevant and interesting, including advertising and marketing messages; to allow you to comment on content,; to provide you with customer support and to respond to inquiries. When the information collected from or about you does not identify you as a specific person, we may use that information for any purpose or share it with third parties.

We use the information we collect from and about you for these additional purposes:

**To allow service providers to assist us in providing and managing the _Ball Ball_ Services.** We may make your information available to certain third party service providers, such as contractors, agents or sponsors, who help us manage or provide the Services.

**To allow social sharing functionality.** If you log in with or connect a social media service account with _Ball Ball_ , we may share your user name, picture, and likes, as well as your activities and comments with other _Ball Ball_ users and with your friends associated with your social media service. We may also share the same information with the social media service provider. By logging in with or connecting your _Ball Ball_ account with a social media service, you consent to us sharing information we collect from and about you with the social media service provider, other users and your friends and you understand that the social media service’s use of the shared information will be governed by the social media service’s privacy policy. If you do not want your personal information shared in this way, please do not connect your social media service account with your _Ball Ball_ account and do not participate in social sharing on the Services.

**To deliver relevant advertisements.** _Ball Ball_ and our service providers may use the information we collect from and about you to deliver relevant ads to you when you use the Services or another service. As noted above, third-party advertising networks and advertisers may use cookies and similar technologies to collect and track information such as demographic information, inferred interests, aggregated information, and activity to assist them in delivering advertising that is more relevant to your interests. To find out more about third-party advertising networks and similar entities that use these technologies, see [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/), and to opt-out of such advertising networks’ and services’ advertising practices, go to [www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices).

**To contact you.** We may periodically send promotional materials or notifications related to the Services. If you want to stop receiving promotional materials, you can change your account settings by emailing [privacy@ballball.com](mailto:privacy@ballball.com) or by following the unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. There are certain service notification emails that you may not opt-out of, such as notifications of changes to the _Ball Ball_ Services or policies. If you have installed a mobile app and you wish to stop receiving push notifications, you can change the settings either on your mobile device or through the app.

**To share with our Affiliates.** _Ball Ball_ may share your information with our Affiliates for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. A link to a website that lists our Affiliates can be found at the beginning of this policy. Users who visit our Affiliates’ services should still refer to their separate privacy policies, which may differ in some respects from this Privacy Policy. NWS Digital Asia Pte. Limited is the entity responsible for the management of the jointly-used personal information.

**To share with business partners.** ****_Ball Ball_ may share your information with business partners to permit them to send you marketing communications consistent with your choices.

**To protect the rights of** _Ball Ball_ **and others.** There may be instances when we may disclose your information, including situations where we have a good faith belief that such disclosure is necessary in order to: (i) protect, enforce, or defend the legal rights, privacy, safety, or property of _Ball Ball_ , our Affiliates or their employees, agents and contractors, as may be imposed by or under the law (including enforcement of our agreements and our terms of use); (ii) protect the safety, privacy, and security of users of the Services or members of the public; (iii) assist in any investigations or proceedings; (iv) comply with the law or legal process; or (v) respond to requests from government authorities or public agencies and such disclosure is necessary in the public interest.

**To complete a merger or sale of assets.** If we sell all or part of our business or make a sale or transfer of assets or are otherwise involved in a merger or transfer of all or a material part of its business, we may transfer your information to the party or parties involved in the transaction as part of that transaction.

**4\. SECURITY**

_Ball Ball_ uses commercially reasonable administrative, technical, personnel and physical measures to safeguard information in its possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure or modification. However, no one can guarantee the complete safety of your information.

**5\. USER ACCESS AND CONTROL**

If you would like to access, review, correct, update, suppress, or otherwise limit our use of your personal information you have previously provided directly to us, you may contact us as outlined in Section 7. In your request, please include your email address, name, address, and telephone number and specify clearly what information you would like to access, change, update, or suppress. We will try to comply with your request as soon as reasonably practicable.

**6\. OTHER IMPORTANT INFORMATION**

**Updates to Privacy Policy.** We may modify this Privacy Policy. Please look at the Effective Date at the top of this Privacy Policy to see when this Privacy Policy was last revised. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will become effective when we post the revised Privacy Policy on the Services.

**Location of Data.** The Services are managed from Singapore. Where personal information is used or processed outside of Singapore, _Ball Ball_ will ensure that the entity receiving the personal information provides a standard of protection that is comparable to the protection under the Personal Data Protection Act in Singapore (“PDPA”). As a result, please read this Privacy Policy with care.

**Linked Services.** The Services may also be linked to sites operated by unaffiliated companies, and may carry advertisements or offer content, functionality, games, alerts, or applications developed and maintained by unaffiliated companies. _Ball Ball_ is not responsible for the privacy practices of unaffiliated companies, and once you leave the Services or click an advertisement you should check the applicable privacy policy of the other service.

**Collection of Personal Financial Information by a Payment Service.** In some cases, we may use an unaffiliated payment service to allow you to purchase a product or make payments (“Payment Service”). If you wish to purchase a product or make a payment using a Payment Service, you will be directed to a Payment Service webpage. Any information that you provide to a Payment Service will be subject to the applicable Payment Service’s privacy policy, rather than this Privacy Policy. We have no control over, and are not responsible for, any Payment Service’s use of information collected through any Payment Service.

**Data Retention.** We will retain your information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy, or until it is reasonable to assume that the purpose for which that personal information was collected is no longer being served by retention of the personal information and retention is no longer necessary for legal or business purposes.

Remember that even after you cancel your account, copies of some information from your account may remain viewable in some circumstances where, for example, you have shared information with social media or other services. Because of the nature of caching technology, your account may not be instantly inaccessible to others. We may also retain backup information related to your account on our servers for some time after cancelation for fraud detection or to comply with applicable law or our internal security policies. It is not always possible to completely remove or delete all of your information due to technical constraints, contractual, financial or legal requirements.

**Sensitive Information.** We ask that you not send us, and you not disclose, any sensitive personal information (such as social security numbers, information related to racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religion or other beliefs, health, criminal background or trade union membership) on or through the _Ball Ball_ Services or otherwise.

**Accuracy**

If your personal information is likely to be used by us to make a decision that affects you, or is likely to be disclosed by us to another organization, we will make reasonable efforts to ensure that the personal information collected by us or on our behalf is accurate and complete. However, our ability to meet this obligation will depend largely on you having provided us with personal information that is accurate and complete.

**Access to Policies and Practices**

Upon your request, we will make available to you information about the policies and practices implemented by us regarding personal data protection and our complaints handling process.

**7\. CONTACT US**

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, or any complaints regarding the handling of your personal information, please contact us at:

Privacy Officer

NWS Digital Asia Pte. Limited,

10 Anson Road, #32-08,

International Plaza,

Singapore 079903

Company registration number: 201318944H
